[
  {
    "id": "T6A01",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What electrical component opposes the flow of current in a DC circuit?",
    "answers": [
      "Inductor",
      "Resistor",
      "Inverter",
      "Transformer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A02",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What type of component is often used as an adjustable volume control?",
    "answers": [
      "Fixed resistor",
      "Power resistor",
      "Potentiometer",
      "Transformer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A03",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What electrical parameter is controlled by a potentiometer?",
    "answers": [
      "Inductance",
      "Resistance",
      "Capacitance",
      "Field strength"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A04",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What electrical component stores energy in an electric field?",
    "answers": [
      "Varistor",
      "Capacitor",
      "Inductor",
      "Diode"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A05",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What type of electrical component consists of conductive surfaces separated by an insulator?",
    "answers": [
      "Resistor",
      "Potentiometer",
      "Oscillator",
      "Capacitor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A06",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What type of electrical component stores energy in a magnetic field?",
    "answers": [
      "Varistor",
      "Capacitor",
      "Inductor",
      "Diode"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A07",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What electrical component is typically constructed as a coil of wire?",
    "answers": [
      "Switch",
      "Capacitor",
      "Diode",
      "Inductor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A08",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What is the function of an SPDT switch?",
    "answers": [
      "A single circuit is opened or closed",
      "Two circuits are opened or closed",
      "A single circuit is switched between one of two other circuits",
      "Two circuits are each switched between one of two other circuits"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A09",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What electrical component is used to protect other circuit components from current overloads?",
    "answers": [
      "Fuse",
      "Thyratron",
      "Varactor",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A10",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following battery chemistries is rechargeable?",
    "answers": [
      "Nickel-metal hydride",
      "Lithium-ion",
      "Lead-acid",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A11",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following battery chemistries is not rechargeable?",
    "answers": [
      "Nickel-cadmium",
      "Carbon-zinc",
      "Lead-acid",
      "Lithium-ion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6A12",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What type of switch is represented by component 3 in figure T-2?",
    "answers": [
      "Single-pole single-throw",
      "Single-pole double-throw",
      "Double-pole single-throw",
      "Double-pole double-throw"
    ]
  }
]